lawyersandsettlements.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy

LAWSUITS NEWS & LEGAL INFORMATION

This Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) explains what Online Legal Media (“OLM”) does with the personally identifiable information that is collected from the users of our website currently located at https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com (the “Site”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Services. By using the Site, you accept the terms of this Policy.

OLM may change its privacy policy from time to time, so it is suggested that you check the Site from time to time to ensure that you know about the current policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should contact us via our [Contact Page](https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com/contact.html).

### Children

If you are under 18, you may not use or access the Site.

### Types of Information We Collect

_Traffic Data_. We may collect a variety of visitor data such as IP addresses, browser settings, internet service provider (ISP) information, referring/exit pages, operating systems, date/time stamps, and clickstream data (collectively, “Visitor Data”). No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. The Site may use Visitor Data to compile traffic data about the types of visitors who use the Site at specific intervals (collectively, “Traffic Data”). We may use Traffic Data to analyze Site traffic, but this information is not examined for personally identifiable information. We may also use Traffic Data to diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, or display content according to your preferences. Visitor Data and Traffic Data may also be shared with business partners, affiliates, or advertisers on an aggregated and anonymous basis.

_Cookies_. We may use the standard cookie feature of major browser applications and third-party providers, including Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting (see below for more information on this), that allow us to store a small piece of data on your computer, or any other device you may use to access the Site, about your use of the Site. Such cookies do capture or mine personally identifiable information. You can remove persistent cookies at any time by following the directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Site but the functionality of the Site may be limited.

_Web Beacons_. We employ web beacons that help us track referrals from our partners and affiliates and better manage content on the Site. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to user’s personally identifiable information.

_Third Party Tracking_. The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners, or other third parties linked to from the Site is not covered by this Policy. Please be aware that these third parties may use cookies, web beacons or other tracking devices, and we do not have access to, or control over, these technologies.

_Personally identifiable information_. We may collect personally identifiable information that you provide in order to access certain features of the Site. Such personally identifiable information includes your name, address, phone number, and email address.

_Data Retention_. OLM will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We may maintain some or all of this data in our archives even after it has been removed from the Site.

### How OLM Uses Your Personally Identifiable Information

OLM will only disclose any personally identifiable information about individual users in accordance with this Policy and our Terms of Service or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of OLM.

OLM discloses personally identifiable information and the other information you provide us to lawyers, law firms, legal financial service providers, or other legal service providers sponsoring the submission forms for the topics to which you respond. OLM cannot guarantee that the information you submit to us will not end up in the hands of third parties, including, without limitation, the entity or person against whom you may have a claim.

OLM may also disclose your contact information and the other information that you provide us in the following circumstances: 

  1. OLM may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Such parties may have access to personally identifiable information if needed to perform their functions, but will not be able to legally use it for other purposes.
  2. OLM might change, sell, reorganize or liquidate its business via bankruptcy. If so, your information may be among the transferred assets or otherwise transferred in a way not contemplated by this Policy. In such event, you will be notified via notice posted to the Site.
  3. OLM may release account and other personally identifiable information when OLM believes such release is appropriate to comply with law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of OLM, our users, or others.

From time to time, OLM may also provide aggregate (statistical) information to third parties to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. If OLM partners with another party to provide a specific service to you, and if you sign up for such service, then and only then will OLM provide your other information to such partner.

### Your Options

We send promotional emails and newsletters from time to time to users who have registered on the Site and to those who have opted in to receive such emails. If you do not wish to receive such communications, please use the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of such communications or send us an email via our [Contact page](https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com/contact.html).

The Site implements Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting for internal purposes only to help us understand the demographics of visitors to the Site and so that we can provide more focused content and ads to our users. You may visit Google Analytics’ Ads Settings to opt out of Google’s use of cookies and customize Google Display Network ads, and Google Analytics’ Opt Out Browser Add-on for the web by clicking here: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922>.

In addition, you may choose not to provide your personally information or you may turn off cookies in your browser by changing its settings (as described above). If you do so, you may continue to use the Site but the services provided by the Site may be limited.

### Third Party Links

We provide links to third party sites. This Policy applies only to the Site and not to other third party sites accessible from the Site, each of which may have privacy policies materially different from this Policy. If you visit third party sites, OLM is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policies of any third party sites to confirm that you understand and agree with such policies.

### Our other Services

OLM may send you occasional notices or newsletters about OLM services unless you tell us not to. If you do not want to receive such offers, you can click the unsubscribe link, which you will find on our email messages, or send an email at any time via our [Contact page](https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com/contact.html).

When you submit information to the Site, you will be sent a complimentary issue of our Class Action and Large Recoveries Newsletter in order to keep you up to date with new class actions and settlements. If you do not wish to receive further issues, please use the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of the newsletter or send us an email via our [Contact page](https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com/contact.html).

### How to Edit the Information OLM Has About You

If you want to correct, change, or delete any information we have about you, please [Contact Us](https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com/contact.html).

### Security

OLM takes reasonable precautions to make certain that our servers and connections incorporate adequate encryption and security devices. We have implemented physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. Personally identifiable information is transmitted by secure servers (SSL). However, no data transmission is guaranteed to be totally secure and we cannot guarantee the security of information you transmit to or from the Site and you provide all such information at your own risk. WE DISCLAIM ALL LIABILITY FOR THE THEFT, LOSS, OR INTERCEPTION OF, OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO, YOUR DATA OR COMMUNICATIONS TRANSMITTED THROUGH THE SITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND ASSUME THESE RISKS.

### Conditions of Use

Any dispute over privacy is subject to our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, venue of disputes, and the application of the laws of the State of California.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or comments about the practices of the Site, or your dealings with us, you may [Contact Us](https://www.lawyersandsettlements.com/contact.html).

LawyersandSettlements.com  
849 Almar Ave.  
Suite C-197  
Santa Cruz, CA 95060  

Last modified 2015-07-29
